{
  "questionSets": [
    {
      "id": "addition_basic",
      "name": "Basic Addition",
      "description": "Single-digit and teen addition practice questions for early battles.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": 1,
          "question": "What is 5 + 8?",
          "options": [
            1,
            13,
            12,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 2,
          "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
          "options": [
            7,
            15,
            12,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 15
        },
        {
          "id": 3,
          "question": "What is 5 + 9?",
          "options": [
            14,
            4,
            9,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 14
        },
        {
          "id": 4,
          "question": "What is 3 + 4?",
          "options": [
            2,
            11,
            18,
            7
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 5,
          "question": "What is 2 + 3?",
          "options": [
            5,
            13,
            18,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 6,
          "question": "What is 5 + 1?",
          "options": [
            6,
            11,
            4,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 7,
          "question": "What is 2 + 1?",
          "options": [
            8,
            1,
            10,
            3
          ],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 8,
          "question": "What is 4 + 3?",
          "options": [
            10,
            9,
            7,
            17
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 9,
          "question": "What is 9 + 7?",
          "options": [
            10,
            4,
            16,
            17
          ],
          "answer": 16
        },
        {
          "id": 10,
          "question": "What is 2 + 8?",
          "options": [
            12,
            13,
            8,
            10
          ],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "id": 11,
          "question": "What is 6 + 5?",
          "options": [
            12,
            10,
            11,
            7
          ],
          "answer": 11
        },
        {
          "id": 12,
          "question": "What is 9 + 4?",
          "options": [
            13,
            12,
            7,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 13,
          "question": "What is 0 + 5?",
          "options": [
            7,
            13,
            6,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 14,
          "question": "What is 0 + 0?",
          "options": [
            8,
            7,
            1,
            10
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 15,
          "question": "What is 1 + 6?",
          "options": [
            17,
            18,
            5,
            7
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 16,
          "question": "What is 9 + 7?",
          "options": [
            4,
            16,
            5,
            17
          ],
          "answer": 16
        },
        {
          "id": 17,
          "question": "What is 1 + 0?",
          "options": [
            13,
            1,
            11,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 18,
          "question": "What is 6 + 0?",
          "options": [
            17,
            1,
            16,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 19,
          "question": "What is 9 + 3?",
          "options": [
            13,
            16,
            12,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 12
        },
        {
          "id": 20,
          "question": "What is 7 + 3?",
          "options": [
            11,
            10,
            18,
            15
          ],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "id": 21,
          "question": "What is 9 + 0?",
          "options": [
            10,
            3,
            15,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 22,
          "question": "What is 1 + 2?",
          "options": [
            6,
            8,
            10,
            3
          ],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 23,
          "question": "What is 3 + 5?",
          "options": [
            6,
            8,
            9,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "id": 24,
          "question": "What is 9 + 5?",
          "options": [
            1,
            14,
            18,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 14
        },
        {
          "id": 25,
          "question": "What is 7 + 1?",
          "options": [
            14,
            2,
            10,
            8
          ],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "id": 26,
          "question": "What is 0 + 9?",
          "options": [
            4,
            7,
            11,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 27,
          "question": "What is 0 + 3?",
          "options": [
            6,
            3,
            16,
            7
          ],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 28,
          "question": "What is 2 + 5?",
          "options": [
            7,
            18,
            1,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 29,
          "question": "What is 9 + 5?",
          "options": [
            14,
            10,
            12,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 14
        },
        {
          "id": 30,
          "question": "What is 0 + 2?",
          "options": [
            10,
            6,
            5,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 31,
          "question": "What is 8 + 6?",
          "options": [
            14,
            5,
            1,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 14
        },
        {
          "id": 32,
          "question": "What is 2 + 6?",
          "options": [
            18,
            3,
            8,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "id": 33,
          "question": "What is 8 + 8?",
          "options": [
            10,
            1,
            3,
            16
          ],
          "answer": 16
        },
        {
          "id": 34,
          "question": "What is 6 + 1?",
          "options": [
            1,
            7,
            5,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 35,
          "question": "What is 9 + 4?",
          "options": [
            13,
            5,
            8,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 36,
          "question": "What is 5 + 0?",
          "options": [
            5,
            16,
            18,
            8
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 37,
          "question": "What is 9 + 3?",
          "options": [
            18,
            2,
            12,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 12
        },
        {
          "id": 38,
          "question": "What is 1 + 8?",
          "options": [
            11,
            4,
            1,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 39,
          "question": "What is 3 + 9?",
          "options": [
            7,
            5,
            12,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 12
        },
        {
          "id": 40,
          "question": "What is 0 + 8?",
          "options": [
            8,
            14,
            11,
            3
          ],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "id": 41,
          "question": "What is 2 + 5?",
          "options": [
            15,
            7,
            12,
            16
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 42,
          "question": "What is 5 + 2?",
          "options": [
            15,
            7,
            9,
            16
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 43,
          "question": "What is 0 + 7?",
          "options": [
            1,
            7,
            8,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 44,
          "question": "What is 8 + 7?",
          "options": [
            4,
            12,
            11,
            15
          ],
          "answer": 15
        },
        {
          "id": 45,
          "question": "What is 7 + 0?",
          "options": [
            15,
            17,
            7,
            18
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 46,
          "question": "What is 0 + 9?",
          "options": [
            10,
            2,
            5,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 47,
          "question": "What is 8 + 5?",
          "options": [
            17,
            5,
            13,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 48,
          "question": "What is 7 + 7?",
          "options": [
            17,
            9,
            13,
            14
          ],
          "answer": 14
        },
        {
          "id": 49,
          "question": "What is 2 + 2?",
          "options": [
            14,
            15,
            4,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 4
        },
        {
          "id": 50,
          "question": "What is 1 + 2?",
          "options": [
            3,
            16,
            10,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 3
        },
        {
          "id": 51,
          "question": "What is 4 + 1?",
          "options": [
            1,
            12,
            14,
            5
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 52,
          "question": "What is 0 + 2?",
          "options": [
            4,
            17,
            8,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 53,
          "question": "What is 4 + 2?",
          "options": [
            13,
            6,
            3,
            4
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 54,
          "question": "What is 8 + 2?",
          "options": [
            8,
            1,
            6,
            10
          ],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "id": 55,
          "question": "What is 6 + 7?",
          "options": [
            15,
            7,
            13,
            14
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 56,
          "question": "What is 6 + 4?",
          "options": [
            10,
            11,
            3,
            8
          ],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "id": 57,
          "question": "What is 0 + 7?",
          "options": [
            7,
            8,
            11,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 58,
          "question": "What is 5 + 4?",
          "options": [
            9,
            15,
            2,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 59,
          "question": "What is 0 + 5?",
          "options": [
            5,
            17,
            2,
            11
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 60,
          "question": "What is 5 + 0?",
          "options": [
            5,
            3,
            9,
            4
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 61,
          "question": "What is 7 + 8?",
          "options": [
            5,
            15,
            1,
            17
          ],
          "answer": 15
        },
        {
          "id": 62,
          "question": "What is 8 + 0?",
          "options": [
            6,
            5,
            8,
            1
          ],
          "answer": 8
        },
        {
          "id": 63,
          "question": "What is 6 + 7?",
          "options": [
            8,
            11,
            13,
            4
          ],
          "answer": 13
        },
        {
          "id": 64,
          "question": "What is 2 + 4?",
          "options": [
            5,
            10,
            12,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 65,
          "question": "What is 5 + 1?",
          "options": [
            16,
            4,
            6,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 66,
          "question": "What is 2 + 3?",
          "options": [
            14,
            1,
            5,
            13
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 67,
          "question": "What is 3 + 2?",
          "options": [
            5,
            14,
            15,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 5
        },
        {
          "id": 68,
          "question": "What is 4 + 6?",
          "options": [
            10,
            17,
            11,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 10
        },
        {
          "id": 69,
          "question": "What is 8 + 7?",
          "options": [
            11,
            15,
            12,
            10
          ],
          "answer": 15
        },
        {
          "id": 70,
          "question": "What is 4 + 3?",
          "options": [
            7,
            11,
            18,
            6
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 71,
          "question": "What is 5 + 4?",
          "options": [
            14,
            18,
            3,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 72,
          "question": "What is 4 + 3?",
          "options": [
            5,
            7,
            15,
            11
          ],
          "answer": 7
        },
        {
          "id": 73,
          "question": "What is 3 + 3?",
          "options": [
            13,
            6,
            5,
            14
          ],
          "answer": 6
        },
        {
          "id": 74,
          "question": "What is 0 + 1?",
          "options": [
            16,
            3,
            1,
            4
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 75,
          "question": "What is 5 + 4?",
          "options": [
            5,
            9,
            3,
            12
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 76,
          "question": "What is 0 + 2?",
          "options": [
            7,
            16,
            14,
            2
          ],
          "answer": 2
        },
        {
          "id": 77,
          "question": "What is 0 + 0?",
          "options": [
            1,
            12,
            6,
            10
          ],
          "answer": 1
        },
        {
          "id": 78,
          "question": "What is 6 + 3?",
          "options": [
            3,
            18,
            17,
            9
          ],
          "answer": 9
        },
        {
          "id": 79,
          "question": "What is 8 + 8?",
          "options": [
            8,
            11,
            2,
            16
          ],
          "answer": 16
        },
        {
          "id": 80,
          "question": "What is 1 + 1?",
          "options": [
            15,
            2,
            1,
            8
          ],
          "answer": 2
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
